[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '泊ります' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とまります"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '練習' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "れんしゅう"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '洗濯' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "せんたく"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '掃除' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "そうじ"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '始まります' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はじまります"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '新型' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しんがた"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '開きます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ひらきます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '会場' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かいじょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '楽しみます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たのしみます"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '大通り' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おおどおり"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '以上' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いじょう"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the kanji '像' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ぞう"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the kanji '競馬' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けいば"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the kanji '恐竜' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "きょうりゅう"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the kanji '建物' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "たてもの"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the kanji '映します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "うつします"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the kanji '映像' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "えいぞう"
    }
]